Garrison Family Papers, 1694-2005 (bulk 1830-1950)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES 1810-1966
  - Harvard University, [See also SERIES VII. PHOTOGRAPHS and SERIES VIII. MEMORABILIA]
    - Class of 1897
      - Reunions
        - 25th1921-22 (Box 180, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence and printed material 1901-57, undated (Box 180, Folder 8)
    - Class of 19281938, 1977-78 (Box 180, Folder 9)
    - D.K.E. 1891-92 (Box 180, Folder 10)
    - Harvard Club of Boston 1913-41 (Box 180, Folder 11)
    - Harvard Endowment Fund 1919 (Box 180, Folder 12)
    - Harvard Graduates' Magazine 1913-14, undated (Box 180, Folder 13)
    - Harvard Liberal Club of Boston 1918-21, undated (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - Harvard Memorial Society 1896-97 (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - Harvard Total Abstinence League 1912, undated (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - Signet 1897-1941, undated (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence and printed material 1895-1960, undated (Box 181, Folder 5-7)
  - Hockey 1925 (Box 181, Folder 8)
  - Homeopathy 1828-1943, undated (Box 181, Folder 9)
  - Immigration restriction, [See also SERIES IV. WRITINGS AND SPEECHES -WLG (1838) and Oversize]
    - Chinese
      - Chinese Defense Fund 1903-04, undated (Box 181, Folder 10)
      - Chinese Equal Rights League 1892 (Box 181, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence (Box 181, Folder 13)
        - Judge Maguire controversy 1871-93 (Box 181, Folder 14)
        - Miscellaneous 1879-1908, undated (Box 181, Folder 14)
      - Printed material
        - Pamphlets and articles 1885-1908, undated (Box 182, Folder 1)
        - Clippings 1879-1907, undated (Box 182, Folder 2-4)
      - Miscellaneous 1889-1921, undated (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - National Liberal Immigration League 1907-08, undated (Box 182, Folder 6)
    - Printed material and correspondence 1894-1924, undated (Box 182, Folder 7)
  - Jackson Homestead 1954, 1956 (Box 182, Folder 8)
  - Massachusetts Heavy Artillery, 1st1898 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology 1916-33, undated (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - Native Americans 1894, undated (Box 183, Folder 3)
  - Organizations
    - American Civil Liberties Union 1918-23, undated (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - American Friends Service Committee
      - Community Relations Committee 1964-67 (Box 183, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous printed material 1964-67, undated (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - Boston League of Women Voters 1919-24 (Box 183, Folder 7)
    - Bostonian Society 1920-21, undated (Box 183, Folder 8)
    - Committee of Manufacturers and Merchants on Federal Taxation 1921-26, undated (Box 183, Folder 9)
    - Engineers Club 1914-19, 1940 (Box 183, Folder 10)
    - Free Religious Association of America 1917-59, undated (Box 183, Folder 11)
    - Italian Political Prisoner Aid Committeeundated (Box 183, Folder 12)
    - League for Democratic Control 1917, undated (Box 183, Folder 13)
    - Massachusetts Audubon Society 1939-48, [See also SERIES VIII. MEMORABILIA- Garrison, David Lloyd- Birding material] (Box 183, Folder 14)
    - Massachusetts Department of Conservation 1937-38 (Box 183, Folder 15)
    - Massachusetts Society of Colonial Dames
      - Correspondence 1950-57, undated (Box 183, Folder 16-17)
      - Miscellaneous printed material and notes 1927-56, undated (Box 183, Folder 18)
    - National Association of Audubon Societies 1921-34 (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - National Civil Liberties Union 1917-23 (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - National Economic League 1917-25, undated (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - National Popular Government League 1918-21, undated (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - Nature Conservancy 1953-60 (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - New England Cooperative Societyundated (Box 184, Folder 6)
    - New England Historic Genealogical Society 1927-64, undated (Box 184, Folder 7)
    - New England Museum of Natural History 1938-46 (Box 184, Folder 8)
    - Nuttall Ornithological Club 1940-72 (Box 184, Folder 9)
    - People's Lobby 1928, undated (Box 184, Folder 10)
    - People's International League for Freedom Through Justice 1926 (Box 184, Folder 11)
    - Russian Reconstruction Farms 1925-28 (Box 184, Folder 12)
    - Society for the Advancement of India 1907-08, undated (Box 184, Folder 13)
    - Sudbury Valley Trustees, Inc. 1956-58 (Box 184, Folder 14)
    - Trotter Golden Testimonial Committee 1919-33 (Box 184, Folder 15)
    - Tuesday Club 1930-39, undated, [See also SERIES IV. WRITINGS AND SPEECHES - WLG (1874)] (Box 184, Folder 16)
    - Union Club of Boston 1914-63, undated (Box 184, Folder 17)
    - University Club 1928-29 (Box 184, Folder 18)
    - Wranglers 1917-21, undated (Box 184, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous, A-Z 1893-1966, undated (Box 185, Folder 1-11)
  - Osteopathy 1906-07 (Box 185, Folder 12)
  - Osterville (MA), [See also SERIES VIII. MEMORABILIA - WLG (1838)]
    - Free Public Library
      - Clippings and printed material 1882-68 (Box 186, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence 1905-67, undated (Box 186, Folder 2)
      - Reports 1905-57 (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - Reunions 1877-78 (Box 186, Folder 4-5)
    - Miscellaneous 1878-1969, undated (Box 186, Folder 6)
  - Pacifism, [See also Single tax -correspondence-Daniel Kiefer]
    - Correspondence and printed material 1907-25, undated (Box 186, Folder 7)
    - Military training 1904-26 (Box 186, Folder 8)
    - Organizations
      - American Union against Militarism
        - Bulletins 1918-20 (Box 186, Folder 9)
        - Correspondence and printed material 1916-20, undated (Box 186, Folder 10)
      - Association to Abolish War 1915-27,undated (Box 186, Folder 11)
      - Fellowship of Reconciliation 1920-23, undated (Box 186, Folder 12)
      - Women's Peace Party 1915-17, undated (Box 186, Folder 13)
      - Women's Peace Society 1920-25, undated (Box 186, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous 1839-1940, undated (Box 186, Folder 15)
  - Periodicals
    - Analysis 1945-49 (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - Antioch News 1929-31 (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - Boston Patriot 1810, [See Flat File]
    - Boston Weekly Transcript 1879, [See Flat File]
    - Daily Evening Transcript 1850, undated, [See Flat File]
    - The Diamond 1851-52 (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - Free Press 1826, [See Flat File]
    - Freeman 1924 (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - Ground Hog 1915-20, undated (Box 187, Folder 5)
    - Herald of Freedom 1835, [bound with 1835 Liberator - SSC Periodicals Collection]
    - Hope and Home 1894-95, [See Flat File]
    - Liberator (Max Eastman, ed.) 1917-18 (Box 187, Folder 6)
    - The New York Evangelist 1850, [See Flat File]
    - Our Home Rights 1904 (Box 187, Folder 7)
    - Proportional Representation Review 1894-95 (Box 187, Folder 8)
    - The Public 1908-09 (Box 187, Folder 9)
    - The Una 1854 (Box 187, Folder 10)
    - Zion's Herald 1835, [bound with 1835 Liberator - SSC Periodicals Collection]
  - Race, [See also SERIES IV. WRITINGS AND SPEECHES - WLG (1838)]
    - Anti-lynching, [See also SERIES III. CORRESPONDENCE - Letters to Garrisons - Willard, Frances]
      - Debate on anti-Lynchingundated (Box 187, Folder 11)
      - Sam Hose Case 1899 (Box 187, Folder 12)
      - Printed material
        - Clippings
          - Scrapbook 1888-94 (Box 187, Folder 13)
          - Miscellaneous 1894-1904, undated (Box 187, Folder 14)
        - Articles, flyers 1893-1935 (Box 187, Folder 15)
        - Daniel H. Chamberlain 1904-08, n.d (Box 187, Folder 16)
    - Education
      - Clippings and pamphlets 1894-1915, undated (Box 188, Folder 1)
      - Berea College 1894-09, undated (Box 188, Folder 2)
      - Calhoun Colored School and Calhoun Club of Boston 1909-26, undated (Box 188, Folder 3)
      - Forsythe Normal and Industrial School
        - Correspondence 1903-13, undated (Box 188, Folder 4-6)
        - Miscellaneous 1902, undated (Box 188, Folder 7)
      - Hampton Normal and Agricultural Institute 1919-21 (Box 188, Folder 8)
      - Temperance, Industrial and Collegiate Institute, [See SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS - Smallwood, John T.]
      - Tuskegee Institute 1895-1930, [See also SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS - Washngton, Booker T. and SERIES III. CORRESPONDENCE -Letters to the Garrisons- Washington, Booker T.] (Box 188, Folder 9)
    - The Exodus 1880, 1881, [See Flat File]
    - Fraternity 1893-94 (Box 188, Folder 10)
    - The Freeman 1895, undated (Box 188, Folder 11)
    - The Guardian 1906, [See Flat File]
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People 1911-26 (Box 188, Folder 12)
    - Negro troops 1898-1906, undated, [See also SERIES XI. SCRAPBOOKS - George T. Garrison, record of the 55th Massachusetts Division] (Box 188, Folder 13)
    - The Race Problem 1897-99 (Box 188, Folder 14)
    - Suffrage 1898-1917, undated (Box 188, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence 1888-1936 (Box 188, Folder 16)
    - Printed material
      - Articles 1895-1924, undated (Box 189, Folder 1)
      - Clippings 1859-1968, undated (Box 189, Folder 2-4)
      - Pamphlets 1893-1928, undated (Box 189, Folder 5)
  - Referendum 1904-05, undated (Box 190, Folder 1)
  - Roxbury Latin School 1894-1943, [See also SERIES VIII. MEMORABILIA - WLG (1874)] (Box 190, Folder 2)
  - St. Louis World's Fair 1902 (Box 190, Folder 3)
  - St. Monica's Home (Rockledge) 1904-61, undated (Box 190, Folder 4)
  - Sidney Lanier Camp 1921-32, undated (Box 190, Folder 5)
  - Single tax, [See also SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS -Johnson, Tom; Fowlds, George; and George, Henry]
    - Congressional Record 1904-16 (Box 190, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence
      - Bachrach, D. 1915-19, undated (Box 190, Folder 7)
      - Daniel, Walter 1916-19, undated (Box 190, Folder 8)
      - Fowlds, George, [See SERIES III. CORRESPONDENCE - Letters to the Garrisons]
      - Garvin, Lucious F. 1915-17 (Box 190, Folder 9)
      - Johnson, Gerrit 1918-20 (Box 190, Folder 10)
      - Kiefer, Daniel 1914-23 (Box 190, Folder 11-13)
      - Padelford, F. Mason 1922-32 (Box 190, Folder 14)
      - Pastoriza, Joseph J. 1914-17, undated (Box 190, Folder 15)
      - Stephens, Frank, [See SERIES III. CORRESPONDENCE - Letters to the Garrisons]
      - Miscellaneous 1894-1931, undated (Box 190, Folder 16)
    - Economic Principles Or How Wealth Is Produced And How It Is Distributed by Eliza Stowe Twitchell: typescript, published pamphlet, and correspondence 1894, [See also SERIES III. CORRESPONDENCE - Letters to the Garrisons - Twitchell, Eliza Stowe] (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - George, Henry: writings and speeches 1877-1921, undated (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - Houston, Texas and Joseph J. Pastoriza 1904-24, undated (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - Land and Labor Library 1887-1916, undated (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - Organizations
      - American Single Tax League 1908-09 (Box 191, Folder 5)
      - Great Adventure League of California 1916-33, undated (Box 191, Folder 6)
      - Henry George Foundation of America 1927-39, .d. (Box 191, Folder 7)
      - Henry George Institute of New England, Inc. 1942, undated (Box 191, Folder 8)
      - Henry George School of Social Science 1935-47, undated (Box 191, Folder 9)
      - Homestead Loan and Land League 1917-18 (Box 191, Folder 10)
      - Joseph Fels Fund 1913-16, undated (Box 191, Folder 11)
      - Manhattan Single Tax Club 1890-30, undated (Box 191, Folder 12)
      - Massachusetts Single Tax League
        - Clippings and pamphlets 1898-1920, undated (Box 191, Folder 13)
        - Correspondence and miscellaneous printed material 1897-1938, undated (Box 191, Folder 14)
        - Joseph J. Pastoriza visit 1916 (Box 191, Folder 15)
        - Reports 1913-17 (Box 191, Folder 16)
      - National Single Tax League 1918-22, undated (Box 192, Folder 1)
      - New York State Single Tax League 1915-17, undated (Box 192, Folder 2)
      - Pueblo (CO) Single Tax League 1913-15, undated (Box 192, Folder 3)
      - Rhode Island Tax Reform Association 1908-15 (Box 192, Folder 4)
      - Robert Schalkenbach Foundation 1927-45, undated (Box 192, Folder 5)
      - Single Tax Party 1919-21, undated (Box 192, Folder 6)
      - United Committee for The Taxation of Land Values
        - Land and Liberty 1928-42, undated (Box 192, Folder 7)
        - Miscellaneous 1908-39 (Box 192, Folder 8)
    - Periodicals
      - The Equitist 1920, undated (Box 192, Folder 9)
      - Henry George Standard 1921-23 (Box 192, Folder 10)
      - Land Values 1904-05 (Box 192, Folder 11)
      - The Liberator (New Zealand.) 1915-30 (Box 192, Folder 12)
      - National Single Taxer 1898-1900, undated (Box 192, Folder 13)
      - Progress 1906-10 (Box 192, Folder 14)
      - The Single Tax Review 1905-28, undated (Box 192, Folder 15)
      - The Speaker 1904-05 (Box 192, Folder 16)
      - The Standard 1888-92 (Box 192, Folder 17)
      - Tax Facts 1922-23 (Box 192, Folder 18)
      - Why 1899-1905 (Box 192, Folder 19)
    - Printed material
      - Articles and pamphlets 1888-1935, undated (Box 192, Folder 20)
      - Clippings 1888-1928, undated (Box 193, Folder 1-3)
      - Pamphlets 1890-1932, undated (Box 193, Folder 4-6)
      - "Quotable authorities" collected by WLG (1838) 1887-1905, undated (Box 193, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous 1897-1932, undated (Box 193, Folder 8)
  - Suffrage
    - "Anti suffrage, last suffrage campaign," undated (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - Conventions 1856, 1870, 1872 (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence 1898-1919, 1952, undated (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - England
      - Clippings 1906-13, undated (Box 194, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, memorabilia, and printed material 1867-1914, undated (Box 194, Folder 5)
      - Memorabilia 1900-50, undated (Box 194, Folder 6)
    - National Citizen 1880, [See Flat File]
    - New Jersey suffrage campaign scrapbook (Marian K. Garrison) 1913-15 (Box 194, Folder 7)
    - Organizations
      - Boston, Equal Suffrage Association for Good Government 1918-19, n.d (Box 194, Folder 8)
      - Empire State Campaign Committee 1915, undated (Box 194, Folder 9)
      - Massachusetts Political Equality Union 1915 (Box 194, Folder 10)
      - Massachusetts Woman Suffrage Association 1898-1917, undated (Box 194, Folder 11)
      - Men's League for Woman Suffrage 1910-15, undated (Box 194, Folder 12)
      - National American Woman Suffrage Association 1904-23, 1950, undated (Box 194, Folder 13)
      - Newton Equal Suffrage League
        - Clippings 1915, undated (Box 194, Folder 14)
        - Correspondence 1913-15, undated (Box 194, Folder 15)
        - Equal suffrage endorsement 1915 (Box 194, Folder 16)
        - Organizational material, membership, fundraising, and notes 1913-16, undated (Box 194, Folder 17)
      - New York State Woman Suffrage Party 1916-17, undated (Box 194, Folder 18)
    - Photographs, [See SERIES VII. PHOTOGRAPHS]
      - Printed material
        - Clippings 1884-1915, undated (Box 195, Folder 1)
        - Pamphlets 1865-1916, undated (Box 195, Folder 2)
        - Miscellaneous 1912-15, undated (Box 195, Folder 3)
        - Woman's Journal 1908-16, (for run of this magazine see SSC Periodicals Collection) (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - Temperance, [See also Harvard University - Harvard Total Abstinence League and SERIES III. CORRESPONDENCE - Letters to the Garrisons - Willard, Frances]
      - Massachusetts Total Abstinence Societyundated (Box 196, Folder 1)
      - National Philanthropist 1828, [See Flat File]
      - Printed material
        - Articles and miscellaneous printed material 1889-1907, undated (Box 196, Folder 2)
        - Clippings
          - Scrapbook 1887-92 (Box 196, Folder 3)
          - Miscellaneous 1886-1908, undated (Box 196, Folder 4-5)
        - Pamphlets 1883-1900, undated (Box 196, Folder 6)
      - Tobacco 1879-96, undated (Box 196, Folder 7)
      - Women's Christian Temperance Union 1919 (Box 196, Folder 8)
    - Wianno, [See also SERIES VII. PHOTOGRAPHS]
      - Blue prints, cottage layouts, house specifications and related correspondence 1917-27, [See also Flat File] (Box 197, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence
        - Coffin, O. C.(maintenance) 1916-22, undated (Box 197, Folder 2)
        - Daniel Brothers Contractors 1905-51, undated (Box 197, Folder 3-4)
        - Daniel, Goodspeed & Co (real estate) 1936-42 (Box 197, Folder 5)
        - H. Nelson Emmons (real estate) 1920-27 (Box 197, Folder 6)
        - Hinckley Electric Co. (electrical contractor) 1920-27 (Box 197, Folder 7)
        - Rosemond, R. V. (boat purchase) 1913 (Box 197, Folder 8)
        - Miscellaneous 1903-50, undated (Box 197, Folder 9)
      - Deeds and titles 1910-22, undated (Box 197, Folder 10)
      - Gypsy moth eradication 1914-19, undated (Box 197, Folder 11)
      - Hurricane 1944 (Box 197, Folder 12)
      - Notes and inventories 1917-43, undated (Box 197, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous 1896-24, undated (Box 197, Folder 14)
    - Wianno Club
      - Correspondence 1904-66 (Box 197, Folder 15)
      - Organization documents 1912-16 (Box 197, Folder 16)
      - Printed material 1916-33, undated (Box 197, Folder 17)
    - World's Columbian Exposition 1891-93 (Box 197, Folder 18)
- SERIES VII. PHOTOGRAPHS 1839-1998
  - Family
    - Bliss
      - Edith Lloyd Garrison ("Yoy") 1913-circa 1950s, undated, [See also Garrison, Francis Jackson] (Box 198, Folder 1)
      - Familycirca 1943-1950s (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Chubb, Marion Knight Garrisonundated (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Emerson
      - Claire Garrison ("Tita") 1904-54, undated (Box 198, Folder 4)
      - Emerson family, circa early 1920s-42 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Garrison
      - Agnes, circa early 1870s-1930s, undated (Box 198, Folder 6)
      - Alice ("Pat") O'Reilly 1945 (Box 198, Folder 7)
      - Annie Catherine Dennis McKim undated, [See also Cased images] (Box 198, Folder 8)
      - Annie Keene Anthony 1873 (Box 198, Folder 9)
      - Charles 1868-1890s, undated, [See also Cased images and Oversize Materials] (Box 198, Folder 10)
      - David Holmes 1899 (Box 198, Folder 11)
      - David Lloyd 1907-98, undated, [See also Oversize Materials and Flat File] (Box 198, Folder 12-13)
      - David Lloyd family 1945-54 (Box 198, Folder 14)
      - Edith Stephenson 1897-1963, [See also Oversize Materials] (Box 199, Folder 1)
      - Eleanorcirca 1883-1974, undated (Box 199, Folder 2)
      - Ellen Wrightcirca 1850s-1930, undated, [See also Cased images] (Box 199, Folder 3)
      - Elizabeth Pease 1848, [See also Cased images] (Box 199, Folder 4)
      - Francis Jackson 1860-1916, undated (Box 199, Folder 5)
      - Francis Jackson family 1894-98, undated (Box 199, Folder 6)
      - Frank Wright 1873-1961, [See also Garrison, Agnes and Oversize Materials] (Box 199, Folder 7)
      - Frank Wright family 1910-29 (Box 199, Folder 8)
      - George Anthony family 1956-70s (Box 200, Folder 1)
      - George Thompson 1860s-72, undated (Box 200, Folder 2)
      - George Thompson family 1881 (Box 200, Folder 3)
      - Helen Bensonundated, [See also Oversize Materials] (Box 200, Folder 4)
      - Jane Wilson, circa late 1920s-60s (Box 200, Folder 5)
      - John Bright 1910-26 (Box 200, Folder 6)
      - John Bright family 1943-51, undated (Box 200, Folder 7)
      - Lloyd McKim 1869-84, undated (Box 200, Folder 8)
      - Lucy McKim 1864-77, [See also Oversize Materials] (Box 200, Folder 9)
      - Margaret Minot Carretundated (Box 200, Folder 10)
      - Mary Pratt 1879-1880s (Box 200, Folder 11)
      - Mildred Yarnall 1920s, undated, [See also Oversize Materials] (Box 200, Folder 12)
      - Philip McKim 1883 (Box 200, Folder 13)
      - Philip McKim family 1900s-10 (Box 200, Folder 14)
      - Robert Hale 1897-14 (Box 200, Folder 15)
      - Theresa Holmes, [See Garrison, Francis J. family]
      - Wendell Holmes 1913 (Box 200, Folder 16)
      - Wendell Phillips 1861-1900, undated, [See also Cased images, Oversize Materials and Flat File] (Box 200, Folder 17)
      - Wendell Phillips family 1870, 1904 (Box 200, Folder 18)
      - William Lloyd (1805), [See also Cased images, and Oversize Materials]
        - Portraits 1864-78, undated (Box 201, Folder 1)
        - Lithographs, prints and, paintings 1846, 1874, undated, [See also Oversize Materials] (Box 201, Folder 2)
        - Family 1860s-89 (Box 201, Folder 3)
        - Sculptures and statues
          - Anne Whitney
            - Bustundated (Box 201, Folder 4)
            - Statue owned by Smith College, [See also Artifacts] (Box 201, Folder 5)
          - Commonwealth Ave, Boston, MA. 1939, undated (Box 201, Folder 6)
          - Newburyport, MAundated (Box 201, Folder 7)
      - William Lloyd (1838) 1856-1908, undated, [See also Cased images and Oversize Materials] (Box 201, Folder 8-10)
      - William Lloyd (1838) family 1867-1963 (Box 201, Folder 11)
      - William Lloyd (1874)circa 1875-1951, undated, [See also Oversize Materials and Artifacts] (Box 202, Folder 1-2)
      - WLG (1874) family 1902-68, undated (Box 202, Folder 3-8)
      - William Lloyd (1902) 1902-50s, n.d., [See also Oversize Materials] (Box 203, Folder 1)
      - WLG (1902) familycirca 1930s-40s (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Harwood
      - Faith Garrison 1911-76, [See also Oversize Materials] (Box 203, Folder 3)
      - Family 1963-75 (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Norton
      - Charles Dyer 1894-1917 (Box 203, Folder 5)
      - Charles Dyer family 1902 (Box 203, Folder 6)
      - Garrison and familycirca 1960s (Box 203, Folder 7)
      - Katherine Garrison (Katz) 1870s-90s, n.d. (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - Phoutrides
      - Aristidesundated (Box 203, Folder 9)
      - Margaret Garrisonundated (Box 203, Folder 10)
    - Stephenson family 1906-27, undated (Box 203, Folder 11)
    - Villard
      - Family 1876 (Box 203, Folder 11a)
      - Fanny (Helen Frances) Garrison 1850s-1920s, undated (Box 203, Folder 12)
      - Harold 1885, undated, [See also Garrison, Willliam Lloyd (1805)] (Box 203, Folder 13)
      - Helen Elise 1879-87, undated, [See also Garrison, Willliam Lloyd (1805)] (Box 203, Folder 14)
      - Henry 1877-89, undated (Box 203, Folder 15)
      - Henry family 1870-90s (Box 203, Folder 16)
      - Henry Hilgardcirca 1880s (Box 203, Folder 17)
      - Oswald Garrison 1870s-92, undated, [See also Garrison, Frank Wright] (Box 204, Folder 1)
      - Oswald Garrison family 1910s-43 (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Wright
      - Davidundated (Box 204, Folder 3)
      - Frankundated, [See also Cased images] (Box 204, Folder 4)
      - Mabel 1874, undated (Box 204, Folder 5)
      - Martha Coffin 1852-70, undated, [See also Cased images] (Box 204, Folder 6)
      - William Pelham 1862, undated, [See also Cased images] (Box 204, Folder 7)
      - Family 1861, undated, [See also Cased images] (Box 204, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneousundated, [See also Cased images] (Box 204, Folder 9)
    - Groups
      - Reunion 1962 (Box 204, Folder 10)
      - Schroon Lake 1908 (Box 204, Folder 11)
      - Thanksgiving 1886, 1961, [See also Oversize Materials] (Box 204, Folder 12)
      - Wianno 1884, undated (Box 204, Folder 13)
      - WLG (1838) 70th birthday1908 (Box 204, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous 1950s-60s, undated, [See also Oversize Materials] (Box 204, Folder 15)
  - Friends and associates
    - Aundated, [See also Oversize Materials] (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Agassiz, Louisundated (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Alfonso XIIIundated (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Anthony, Susan B., [See Subjects-Suffrage-Groups]
    - B 1863-90, 1920-25, undated, [See also Cased images] (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Berenson, Senda (Abbott)circa 1950, [See also Garrison family groups] (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Birney 1862-66, undated (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - Brown
      - Anna Temple 1868, undated (Box 205, Folder 7)
      - Johnundated (Box 205, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneousundated (Box 205, Folder 9)
    - Browning, Robertundated (Box 205, Folder 10)
    - Buffum 1887, undated (Box 205, Folder 11)
    - Butler, Josephine 1875 (Box 205, Folder 12)